<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Loconomics</title>
    <link>https://loconomics.com/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Loconomics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://loconomics.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Communities</title>
      <link>https://loconomics.com/pages/communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loconomics.com/pages/communities/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loconomics for Higher Education</title>
      <link>https://loconomics.com/pages/higher-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loconomics.com/pages/higher-education/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workforce Development</title>
      <link>https://loconomics.com/pages/workforce-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loconomics.com/pages/workforce-development/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help</title>
      <link>https://loconomics.com/pages/help/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 19:31:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loconomics.com/pages/help/</guid>
      <description>What do you mean by member-owned?We&#39;re 100% owned by members like you – freelancers, 1099 workers, and licensed professionals. Not investors. That means each member shares in the profits and has the right to run for and vote for the board of directors.Legally, we&#39;re a California Cooperative Corporation. Our bylaws ensure control and profits remain in your hands for eternity.Can anyone join?Loconomics membership requires that you are your own boss – that&#39;s it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessibility Policy</title>
      <link>https://loconomics.com/pages/accessibility-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loconomics.com/pages/accessibility-policy/</guid>
      <description>Loconomics Cooperative, Inc. is committed to ensuring accessibility of its website and intranet to people with disabilities.We meetWCAG 2.0 Guidelines, Conformance Level AA and comply with Section 508 guidelines.This policy will be reviewed annually on or before the 1st of October. This policy was last reviewed on October 1st, 2017.Should you find any accessibility issues, please email us atsupport@loconomics.com, and we will do our best to resolve it in a timely manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Background Check Policy</title>
      <link>https://loconomics.com/pages/background-check-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loconomics.com/pages/background-check-policy/</guid>
      <description>1. IntroductionLoconomics Cooperative has designed this Background Check and License Verification Policy (this &amp;#8220;Policy&amp;#8221;) withthe goal of helping Clients feel at ease when scheduling Service Professionals, while creating workopportunities for Service Professionals that may have been served by our justice system. Loconomicsintends to facilitate the provision of Services in a manner that is both informed and fair. In mostcases, Background Checks will be done only at the option of the Service Professional, and Loconomicswill not perform a Background Check without the consent of the Service Professional.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Associate Agreement</title>
      <link>https://loconomics.com/pages/business-associate-agreement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loconomics.com/pages/business-associate-agreement/</guid>
      <description>1. Status of the PartiesThe parties hereby acknowledge and agree that a Service Professional (when applicable) is subject to HIPAA compliance asa covered entity or as a business associate &amp;#8220;Covered Entity,&amp;#8221; and that Loconomics &amp;#8220;BusinessAssociate&amp;#8221; may be a Business Associate of Covered Entity under the HIPAA Security and PrivacyRule and the HITECH Act, each defined below.WHEREAS, Sections 261 through 264 of the federal Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996, Public Law104-191 &amp;#8220;HIPAA&amp;#8221;, known as &amp;#8220;the Administrative Simplification provisions,&amp;#8221;direct the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fees</title>
      <link>https://loconomics.com/pages/fees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loconomics.com/pages/fees/</guid>
      <description>1. Client Booking FeesLoconomics currently charges Clients a first-time scheduling fee of 10% of the cost of scheduled services up to a maximumof $10.00 the first time they schedule with each new Service Professional. There is no schedulingfees for subsequent bookings with the same Service Professional.2. Owner User FeesLoconomics currently charges Service Professionalsmonthly or annual user fees to cover the costs of using the platform and running the cooperative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>https://loconomics.com/pages/terms-of-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loconomics.com/pages/terms-of-service/</guid>
      <description>1. IntroductionWelcome to Loconomics.These Terms of Service (“Agreement”) contain the terms on which Loconomics Cooperative, Inc. (“Loconomics” or “LoconomicsCooperative”), a California Consumer Cooperative Corporation, offers you access towww.loconomics.com, an internet platform (”Website&#34;) and mobile application (“Loconomics Application”).Loconomics Cooperative owns and operates this Website, the Loconomics Application, the mobile andtouch versions of the Website, and any individual websites or service-professional-specific, city-specific,or other area-specific websites we have now or in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press</title>
      <link>https://loconomics.com/pages/press/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 15:35:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loconomics.com/pages/press/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About us</title>
      <link>https://loconomics.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 12:12:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loconomics.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Our MissionLoconomics empowers independent professionals with technology, shared ownership, and connections. Whatever your specialty, we&#39;ve created a platform that puts you first.We&#39;re dedicated to our members, who provide helpful, creative, and meaningful services to the Bay Area and beyond.Our cooperative model means that every profesional is an owner and has an equal vote in the election of the Loconomics board, consisting of fellow professionals, and in other major decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://loconomics.com/pages/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 12:12:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loconomics.com/pages/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>1. IntroductionPlease note that all capitalized terms not defined in this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) are defined in theTerms of Service.This Privacy Policy describes:What information we collectHow we use informationWhen and why we disclose informationYour privacy choicesHow we store and secure informationThis Privacy Policy does not apply to any products or services offered by third parties and made available through the LoconomicsService.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>